Max Handley's Curriculum Vitae

Synopsis

I'm seeking full time employment for the foreseeable future around Mullumbimby. I have my RSA, I own a large van, tools and a driver's license. I'm experienced in multiple construction trades, able to assist in lifting. I have an energetic, inquisitive and professional nature when interacting with staff and patrons, having worked as a sales assistant for many years.

Personal **Details**

DOB: 30/05/1997

Email: maxhandley97@gmail.com

Mobile: 0422067765

Address: 209 Pocket Road, Billinudgel

Education

Bishop Druitt College, Coffs Harbour: 2009–2015 Commerce at University of Melbourne: 2017-2018 Design at University of Melbourne: 2018–2019

Experience

Formwork Carpenter, Knipe Concreting, Byron Bay: 2023 Carpenter, Byron & Beyond Fencing, Byron Bay: 2022-2023 Builder's Assistant, Lakshmi Pty Ltd, Byron Bay: 2022 Labourer, Glen Scheibe Stonemasonry, Mullumbimby: 2020-2022 Lift Attendant, Thredbo Kosciuszko Pty Ltd, Thredbo: 2019 Sales Assistant, Dan Murphy's, Brunswick East: 2017-2019 Surf Teacher, The University of Melbourne Surf Club: 2017-2019 Surf Teacher, Wavetours Surfcamps, Vieux-Boucau, France: 2016 Fit Technician, The Athlete's Foot, Coffs Harbour: 2013-2016 Sales Assistant, Wendy's, Coffs Harbour: 2011-2013

Availability Currently available to work any time with appropriate notice

Referees

Joss Knipe, Knipe Concreting: 0404116924

Liam Kelly, Byron & Beyond Fencing: 0422207299

Glen Scheibe, Stonemason: 0413718420

Paul Nicholson-Smythe, Professional referee: 0497208611